http://www.siteware.ch/webresources/privacy.html

Privacy Statement
Siteware Technologies has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the web site Web Resources by Siteware Technologies.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your host name and IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. Your host name is also used to gather broad demographic information.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Siteware Technologies is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes forums and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Contacting Siteware Technologies
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact .
Parts of this document have been generated by LinkExchange Privacy Wizard.
Copyright © 1997-2005 by Christoph Rüegg.
All rights reserved.
[ Copyright Information ] [ Privacy Statement ]
